You Can Be Anything turns a personal profile,
an opening line, and five choices into a complete story.
I enter a protagonist, MBTI, visual style, mood,
genre, and an original opening sentence.
GPT-5.6 Luna is the default story engine.
The first request creates three contextual choices.
After I choose, Luna writes two story paragraphs
that continue my opening instead of starting over.
The selected scene and its established facts become
context for Growth and the next three choices.
Every decision triggers one advance request,
so the Crisis responds to the path I actually selected.
The same continuity carries through Climax.
Unselected branches do not consume long-form output.
Resolution completes a six-request live cycle:
one initial choice request and five story advances.
The finale preserves my path under Origin, Growth,
Crisis, Climax, Resolution, and Epilogue.
Each playthrough has one session ID and one archive,
containing readable story text and structured history.
Finale illustration is optional.
The game shows the maximum cost before any request.
I used GPT-5.6 through Codex to implement the Luna proxy,
validation, cost-aware caching, and session archives.
The completed image is attached to the same session
as its story, while duplicate requests remain blocked.
Every path becomes a story worth keeping.